<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SVNCRWNS</title>
    <description>SVNCRWNS is a strategy and production company based in Baltimore, MD. We use our skills and resources to work with clients to push their missions forward.  Services include Creative Direction, Strategy, Image Making and Web Design + Development
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 15:43:03 -0400</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 15:43:03 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.6.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Custom Web Sites w/ CMS</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite pieces of art are photo-journalism pieces.  I wish there was more photography on display at more contemporary art spaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see paintings like these all the time.  Initially, I didn’t quite get how solid colors on canvas were considered art, but as I’ve gotten more educated in the art space,  I do understand that this expands on the genres of art culture and criticism.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/journal/custom-web-sites-w-cms/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/custom-web-sites-w-cms/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SVNCRWNS.com - We've changed things up a bit</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-home-page&quot;&gt;The Home Page&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This was the first place we started.  We knew as a creative company, as problem solvers that looking at our website wasn’t very informative, there wasn’t a story.  There was cool work, but how did these things tie together to make up a company?  How does the company work?  How can I work with this company?   These were questions that we were getting from our peers.  It was too abstract.  So we added some color and images, and more transparency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Original&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post-svncrwns-changed-002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Original Home Page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The New Home page&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post-svncrwns-changed-003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The New Home Page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another important point, we removed “strategy + production” and updated it to “We’re a production space”.  That’s still a working title, but the most important idea here is that we’re streamlining things and we’re making our brand easier to understand, easier to digest.  We took the “Featured Projects” section, and added images.  Seems like a small detail, but imagery gave our projects more life, and to the end user, they’re more likely to view our work, see our skills and be interested in supporting more of what we’re doing in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We added a quick link “View our Portfolio” that links to the “Work” page because that’s the most important page for this platform.   Beside the quick link, we added a sign up form for our newsletter, so our users know we’re interested in talking to them more.  We want to start building an audience around our work, so this feature is also very important to our company’s goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-overlay&quot;&gt;The Overlay&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our initial overlay wasn’t very informative.  At the very top was the main menu for the website, and after that section - there is the complete list of our work portfolio for our production company.  Unless our new users, who know nothing about our company, had about 3 hours to spend browsing our films, photoshoots and websites, they would’nt be able to learn much., which resulted in really high bounce rates based on our site analytics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Original&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post-svncrwns-changed-004.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Original Home Page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The New Overlay menu&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post-svncrwns-changed-005.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Original Home Page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We removed the main menu and made it a fixed menu to be visible anywhere on the site.  We organized our portfolio work into two categories, client work and in-house projects.  We added tags to our work so users can have an idea of what kind of work they are about to view.  The overlay menu is visible on all pages, positioned in the lower right hand corner.  We also made the overlay button animated. Before, there were two images, that never really lined up as perfectly as we wanted.  The animations and organization here, should drastically improve our bounce rates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-work-page&quot;&gt;The Work Page&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the Work page.  We added this page to highlight all work that has been completed this year, 2018.  Seeing the activity our company has on this page, along with category tags such as photo and film, and work-space tags that let you know if the project is client or in-house - this information really shares an aerial view of how we’ve evolved in this third year of business.  Many people choose their companies, our company chose us.  During interesting times, it was birthed.  Our very first production, which is in post-production, is a documentary feature that was inspired due to real events happening in our home city, Baltimore, during the April 2015 Uprising in lieu of the death of Freddie Gray and the all-time high rate of police violence against black citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After completing the initial production, to setup our story and interview our contributors, we took action in our city, looking for opportunities to help businesses using a skillset that’s both creative and driven by results.  Through lots of trial and error over the last two years, we’ve learned how to be valuable assets to businesses that were interested in growing and tackling unseen opportunities.  As we go into this next year, with a more refined approach, we’re turning our skills inward and will be focusing more on our in-house projects to move our company forward.  We have lots of ideas for unseen opportunities that we can tackle for ourselves.  We have projects in post-production that we’re finalizing, and we are learning how to use our business skills to launch and grow brands under our own domain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post-svncrwns-changed-006.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Work Page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-journal-page&quot;&gt;The Journal Page&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Journal page is where we share ideas, we share things we make in the studio and we evoke conversations based on our insights.  Because of our experience, we have lots of information to share about branding, about producing content, and using your  identity as a company to grow and reach new markets.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post-svncrwns-changed-007.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Journal Page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-contact-page&quot;&gt;The Contact Page&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before, we just had an email address, now we have more context here, plus contact information.  All of pages are following a design system.  We’re making all the pieces more cohesive, through and through the entire brand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post-svncrwns-changed-008.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Contact Page&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keep checking in to SVNCRWNS as we add more projects to our portfolio and define our story as a production company creating riveting content and making a voice for ourselves.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;call-to-action-on-every-page&quot;&gt;Call to Action on Every Page&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We added a call to action section at the bottom of each page to let our users know what else should be explored.  Users stumble across our site from SEO, social media, client referrals and more.  After finding our website, we want to make sure we highlight the important areas of exploration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/call-to-action.png&quot; alt=&quot;Call to Action&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/journal/svncrwns-we-changed-things-up/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/svncrwns-we-changed-things-up/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Co-founder, Von Lee X Stylist + Designer, @kenjgalaxy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 002&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 002&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 003&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 004&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 005&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 006&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 007&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 008&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 008&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 008&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 008&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 008&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 008&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 008&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_chavonlee_kenj_v15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chavon Lee x Ken J 008&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;caption_wrapper&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;editorial-caption-title&quot;&gt;Von Lee x @kenjgalaxy Credits&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;editorial_caption&quot;&gt;Photography: SVNCRWNS&lt;br /&gt;Stylist: @kenjgalaxy&lt;br /&gt;Muse: Von Lee&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/journal/chavon-lee-x-ken-j/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/chavon-lee-x-ken-j/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SVNCRWNS does Brooklyn Museum</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 001&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 002&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favorite pieces of art are photo-journalism pieces.  I wish there was more photography on display at more contemporary art spaces.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 003&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 004&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 005&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 006&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 007&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 008&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 009&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 010&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see paintings like these all the time.  Initially, I didn’t quite get how solid colors on canvas were considered art, but as I’ve gotten more educated in the art space,  I do understand that this expands on the genres of art culture and criticism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 011&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 012&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 015&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Infinite Blue: One of my favorite collections&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 013&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_14.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 014&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_16.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 016&quot; /&gt;
Artist statements are considered art too!  This statement resonated so deeply, also watched the Matrix Trilogy right after visiting this exhibit&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_bk_museum_17.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS Does BK Museum 017&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/journal/svncrwns-visits-bk-museum/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/svncrwns-visits-bk-museum/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Production Company is Branding Itself</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;5-things-we-considered-to-brand-ourselves&quot;&gt;5 Things We Considered to Brand Ourselves&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We hate to admit it but we were too busy helping other brands tell their story, we’re just now getting around to defining ourselves as a brand and we’re going to share the whole process.  We figured this would be a great resource to our community, to see how a brand is created in ideation and visualized with look, feel and personality during the brand identity phase.  Let’s get into it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;One — Social Media&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Social Media is the biggest elephant in the room, so we tackled it first.  We started with sharing who we are and what we’ve been up to.  We missed this freebie when we first started in 2015.  Realizing how valuable it is to share your process and growth with your audience, we’ve started our &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.instagram.com/svncrwns&quot;&gt;instagram&lt;/a&gt; account and we’re sharing our portfolio.  We have projects as far back as 2015 that we haven’t really talked much about, it was a good time to revisit some of that content and share those stories.  Follow our instagram account, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.instagram.com/svncrwns&quot;&gt;@svncrwns&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_brandcompany.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Brand Company 001&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Two — Logo&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second marketing tool we tackled was our logo.  We wanted it to have a fresher feel, still very minimal but bold.  We just tweaked a few things.  There is more room to explore later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Three — Brand Book&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In order to refresh ourselves on our business vocabulary, we started developing a brand book to make sure we are accurately envisioning our goals, look and feel within our logo and within the entire brand.  So far, we have tackled our vision, target market, personas, brand colors, similar companies that we align ourselves with and a few more details.  Stay tuned for the SVNCRWNS Brand Book, it will be available for download soon.  Make sure you are subscribed to the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.svncrwns.com/newsletter&quot;&gt;newsletter&lt;/a&gt; to receive updates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Four — Strategy&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We created a mind map to strategize our business for the next 5 years.  We thought of every possible idea that seemed innovative, necessary and effective to culture and figured out how to tie it in with our business model.  We also factored in play time.  We love working with our clients, but our production company is also a space to create our own art.  Some of the things we tied in - wanting a streetwear brand, wanting to open a studio/workspace, wanting to do collaborations with other agencies in the space of fashion, art and + culture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Five — Pricing Model&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, we have the makings of a solid blueprint for our business. Our portfolio was also a major asset.  When we weren’t sure what kind of work we actually wanted to do, it was hard convincing people to let us work with them on their businesses.  We started shopping our portfolio as proof of our capabilities.  Based on our portfolio, we looked at the services and products we loved working on the most, and created a pricing model to help with pitching to clients more efficiently.  The pricing model along with the other tools give a more complete look of our business.  When added to the brand book, it allows us to communicate the fine details of our company in the form of a magazine spread that covers who we are, why we exist, and how we make money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bonus&quot;&gt;Bonus&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Six — Website&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are not that advanced that we don’t need websites.  Never under estimate the power of having your own domain online.  It is your very own platform to communicate with your audience.  Update your website with information to ease your customer’s experience.  Show your work.  Share your brand identity.  Share your products / services.  Share where people can find you online.  Share your contact info.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Seven — Portfolio&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is mandatory, this was also the first thing that we created as a company.  We knew that having a solid portfolio would birth our company and show the value we can add to any brand or space.  Having a portfolio to shop to clients is a great asset.  We live in a very instantaneous society, proof of concept is more important than ever.  Have your portfolio ready and accessible for any and every one to see.  To see our portfolio, click on the menu button, showing seasons one through four.
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;archive_header js_scroll_reveal&quot;&gt;
    Resources
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check below for some online resources that we found to be helpful:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A. &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.flipsnack.com/how-to-create-a-brand-book-guide-and-examples/&quot;&gt;How to Create a Brand Book&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;B. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.entrepreneur.com/article/299952&quot;&gt;7 Brand Strategies for E-Commerce Brands, Really All Brands&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;C. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.entrepreneur.com/topic/branding&quot;&gt;Branding Topic - List of Articles on Entrepreneur.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;D. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/jerrymclaughlin/2011/12/14/a-simple-blueprint-for-a-successful-brand/#2d4767b05484&quot;&gt;A Simple Blueprint for Successful Brands&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/journal/branding-our-business/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/branding-our-business/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Event Recap &amp;#58; Delicate</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_delicate_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Delicate Event Recap 002&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_delicate_3.png&quot; alt=&quot;Delicate Event Recap 003&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_delicate_4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Delicate Event Recap 004&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_delicate_5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Delicate Event Recap 005&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_delicate_6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Delicate Event Recap 006&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_delicate_7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Delicate Event Recap 007&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_delicate_8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Delicate Event Recap 008&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_delicate_9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Delicate Event Recap 009&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_delicate_10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Delicate Event Recap 010&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/journal/delicate/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/delicate/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Engagement: Love on Display</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_javoni_stevie_4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Javoni + Stevie Engagement 004&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_javoni_stevie_5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Javoni + Stevie Engagement 005&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_javoni_stevie_6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Javoni + Stevie Engagement 006&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_javoni_stevie_7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Javoni + Stevie Engagement 007&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_javoni_stevie_8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Javoni + Stevie Engagement 008&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_javoni_stevie_9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Javoni + Stevie Engagement 009&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_javoni_stevie_10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Javoni + Stevie Engagement 010&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_javoni_stevie_11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Javoni + Stevie Engagement 011&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_javoni_stevie_12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Javoni + Stevie Engagement 012&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/journal/javoni-and-stevie-engagement/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/javoni-and-stevie-engagement/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Creating Content with Beauty Brand + Ambassador, @shonnawatkins</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_shonnawatkins_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shonna Watkins 001&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_shonnawatkins_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shonna Watkins 002&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_shonnawatkins_3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shonna Watkins 003&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_shonnawatkins_4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shonna Watkins 004&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_shonnawatkins_5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shonna Watkins 005&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_shonnawatkins_6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shonna Watkins 006&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_shonnawatkins_7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Shonna Watkins 007&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;caption_wrapper&quot;&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;editorial-caption-title&quot;&gt;Shonna Watkins Credits&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;editorial_caption&quot;&gt;Photography: SVNCRWNS&lt;br /&gt;Concept: SVNCRWNS&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/journal/shonna-watkins/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/shonna-watkins/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>City of Gods x Light City Baltimore</title>
        <description>&lt;div style=&quot;padding:56.25% 0 0 0;position:relative;&quot;&gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/306005679?portrait=0&quot; style=&quot;position:absolute;top:0;left:0;width:100%;height:100%;&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; mozallowfullscreen=&quot;&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/api/player.js&quot;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Photography + Videography: SVNCRWNS&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/journal/city-of-gods-light-city/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/city-of-gods-light-city/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>SVNCRWNS X Creative Mornings Baltimore</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We were invited to talk at Creative Mornings in Baltimore, MD about the theme of “Context”.  We touched on our recent trip to Los Angeles to visit abstract artist, Mark Bradford, and talked about what our work means to us and what inspires us to continue to focus on building and expanding on community resources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/dist/images/post_creative_mornings.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;SVNCRWNS X Creative Mornings &amp;quot;Context&amp;quot; Keynote&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out our talk by way of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.localcolorpodcast.com/2018/01/26/episode-51-creative-mornings-panel/&quot;&gt;Local Color Podcast&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/journal/creative-mornings/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/journal/creative-mornings/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
